# Matheus Kuster

### Frontend Engineer I Linkedin

Web developer with over 2 years of frontend experience who is comfortable working with the latest technologies and is always trying to reach the next level. Looking for an opportunity to work at a company like Mediaocean with a positive mission to power the world for both marketers and consumers.

## Experience

#### kea.cloud

Frontend Engineer I 2021 - Present

- Created a full component library based on design system.
   100% tested + CI/CD + Storybook.
- Scaled and architected main call center product from a simple Chrome extension to a robust web application.
- Built integrations with Twilio, VGS and Datadog.

#### Barnraiser

Frontend Engineer I 2020 - 2021 (few months)

- Helped on the SSR transformation from their website.

#### Vulcanet

Frontend Engineer | 2020 - 2021

- Recruited 3 frontend developers to join the team.
- Helped in the performance drilling and fixes which leaded to a huge impact in customer's satisfaction.
- Designed and architected internal CRUD dashboards to boost the collaborators productivity.
- Brought Whatsapp, Instagram and MessageBird features integrations.

## Skills

Performance drilling

Good partnership with team & designer

Clean code

Feature design

Professional English

Good problem solver

Helpful when needed

Proactive

#### Education

#### Vila Velha University

Computer Science 2021 - Present

#### uiBoost

UI/UX Design 2020 - 2020

## **RS' Ignite Bootcamp**

Fullstack Development - 9.8/10 2018 - 2019

## Federal Institute of Espirito Santo

Computer Technician - 8.8/10 2017 - 2019

## Achievements

#1 out of 77 in AE's SWE Contest

# Software & Applications

## <u>Development</u>

JavaScript (ES6) Git

Typescript Storybook
HTML/CSS/SCSS GraphQL
React (+Next) Figma

React Native Jest & Cypress

#### Cloud

Google Cloud Github Actions

AWS Datadog
Digital Ocean Sentry

**Other** 

UNIX Twilio
NPM Hotjar
Yarn SSR